<resources>
    <string name="app_name">midnight_chevves</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>
    <string name="first_and_last_name">First and Last Name</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to Cart</string>
    <string name="checkout">Proceed to Checkout</string>
    <string name="cash_on_delivery">Cash on Delivery</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="residential">Residential</string>
    <string name="office">Office</string>
    <string name="location">Get Location</string>
    <string name="change">Change Location</string>


    <string-array name="payment_method_array">
        <item>GCash</item>
        <item>Cash on Delivery</item>
        <item>BDO</item>
        <item>BPI</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="about1">
        "It’s late at night and everyone’s asleep. What are you craving for?"
    </string>
    <string name="about2">
    "TMC came from the idea of experimenting with cooking and baking in the middle of the night. Really, it’s a passion project from an aspiring chef (thus the spelling of “chevves”) who loves food a little too much to the point that she equates receiving food with contentment and high spirits.

        From this, TMC aims to share the same effect to others with their homemade creations and someday be able to help others through it. You know what they say — Always aim for the stars!"
    </string>
    <string name="about3">
    "The siblings chevves that bring the midnight magic! On the right side is hypeman and media extraordinaire Jerico Rillo, bringing not only the best of vibes but the best of products.
        On the left side is the woman behind it all, the aspiring chef and midnight connoisseur, Trishia Rillo! Her love of food may transcend the night but you can be she brings the highest of spirits.
"
    </string>

    <string name="about4">
        "Day or night, birthday or non-birthday. Whether it's a craving or a gift for a loved one, The Midnight Chevves will deliver the best of the best."
    </string>

    <string name="about5">
        "Interested in our newest releases? Follow our social media accounts and stick around for more updates!"
    </string>

</resources>